柯克：舰长日志，星历5029.5
KIRK: Captain's log, stardate 5029.5.
响应我们在提拉库斯星的科学殖民地发出的求救信号
Responding to a distress call from our scientific colony on Triacus,
我们正传送到这里进行调查
we are beaming down to investigate.
斯塔恩斯教授？
Professor Starnes?
我是柯克
It's Kirk.
他死了，舰长
He's dead, Captain.
他似乎不认识我
He didn't seem to know me.
氰碘
Cyalodin.
自伤的
Self-inflicted.
斯塔恩斯：必须摧毁我们自己，外星人降临到我们身上
STARNES: Must destroy ourselves. Alien upon us.
敌人来自内部！敌人！
The enemy from within! The enemy!
所有这一切，都是自己造成的
All this. Self-inflicted.
大规模自杀
Mass suicide.
[儿童的声音]
[CHILDREN'S VOICES]
你没有! 你没打中我！
You did not! You missed me!
你好，你是谁？
Hi. Who are you?
- 我是星舰企业号的柯克  - 我是汤米·斯塔恩斯
- Kirk of the starship Enterprise. - I'm Tommy Starnes.
呃...这是玛丽，史蒂夫，雷和唐
Er... This is Mary, Steve, Ray and Don.
来吧，和我们一起玩，来吧
Come on. Play with us. Come on.
♪ 环绕玫瑰色，波西的口袋 ♪
♪ Ring around the rosy, pocketful of Posey ♪
♪ 灰烬，灰烬，我们都倒下了 ♪
♪ Ashes, ashes, we all fall down  ♪
[孩子们笑着尖叫]
[CHILDREN LAUGH AND SCREAM]
♪ 环绕玫瑰色，波西的口袋 ♪
♪ Ring around the rosy, pocketful of Posey ♪
♪ 灰烬，灰烬，我们都倒下了 ♪
♪ Ashes, ashes, we all fall down ♪
柯克：宇宙，最后的边疆
KIRK: Space, the final frontier.
这些是星舰企业号的航程
These are the voyages of the starship Enterprise.
它的五年任务：探索未知的新世界
Its five-year mission: To explore strange new worlds,
寻找新生命和新文明
to seek out new life and new civilizations,
勇踏前人未至之境
to boldly go where no man has gone before.
柯克：舰长日志，补充
KIRK: Captain's log, supplementary.
我们已经埋葬了斯塔恩斯探险队的成员
We have buried the members of the Starnes exploration party.
每个人都被这里发生的事情深深影响了
Everyone has been deeply affected by what has happened here,
但有一些重要的例外
with some important exceptions.
我们去玩吧
Let's go and play.
- 没有悲伤的迹象？  - 没有任何类型的迹象
- No sign of grief? - No indication of any kind.
- 恐惧？  - 他们似乎完全不害怕
- Fear? - They seem completely unafraid.
- 你坚持认为这是创伤性休克？  - 我不坚持，但这是可能的
- You insist it's traumatic shock? - I don't insist but it's possible.
一个孩子压抑着父母双亡的事实？我不相信
A child suppresses the fact that both parents are dead? I can't believe it.
人类确实有选择性相信的能力
Humans do have a capacity for believing what they choose
不去想痛苦的东西
and excluding what is painful.
- 不是这些孩子，这太不可思议了  - 他们看到了难以置信的东西
- Not these children. It's incredible. - What they saw is incredible.
看过那些死亡的惨状，任何反应都是可能的，包括记忆缺失
The way those deaths occurred, any reaction is possible, including amnesia.
这是我的诊断，在进行具体测试之前，我保留意见
That's my diagnosis. Until specific tests can be made, it remains that.
目前，我将以这一观点为指导
I'll be guided by that opinion, for the present.
要不问问他们？
What about questioning them?
创伤减弱前不要问
Not until traumatization weakens
或者你想出另一种解释
or you come up with another explanation.
强迫他们看这个经历可能会导致永久性损害
Forcing them to see this experience could cause permanent damage.
同意，医生
Accepted, Doctor.
小心
Be careful.
我...对不起，柯克舰长
I'm... I'm sorry, Captain Kirk.
孩子？听我说，很晚了，是时候上船了
Children? Listen to me. It's late and it's time to go up to the ship.
哦，还没有
Oh, not yet.
- 我们才刚刚开始玩得开心  - 现在不行
- We're just beginning to have fun. - Not now.
抱歉，你们得和医生一起上去
I'm sorry. You'll go up with the doctor.
来吧，是时候出发了
Come on. It's time to be going.
这里发生的事情只有那些孩子们知道
Whatever happened here is locked up inside those children.
对斯塔恩斯小队的攻击肯定是无端的
The attack on Starnes' party must surely have been unprovoked.
攻击？看起来似乎是大规模自杀
Attack? Mass suicide is what it seems to be.
我认错，诱发将是一个更精确的术语
I stand corrected. Induced would be a more precise term.
由外力诱发
Induced by an outside force.
- 比如？  - 细菌的释放
- Such as? - The release of bacteria.
或是无助的精神抑郁和有自杀倾向的焦虑的状态
Or a helpless mental depression and a state of suicidal anxiety
可能是由化学诱导的
could have been chemically induced.
是什么能让孩子们免疫？
What would make the children immune?
我不知道，但这是可能的
I do not know. But it is possible.
孩子们可以通过有意识的设计来豁免
The children would have been exempted by conscious design.
- 我会说，这是一个合逻辑的假设  - 他们现在的行为可以用
- A valid assumption, I would say. - And their present behavior
对惩罚的恐惧来解释。
explained by a fear of punishment.
或是对奖励的承诺
Or the promise of reward.
一个未知的袭击者攻击
An attack by an unknown assailant
一个无人居住的星球
on an uninhabited planet.
就我们所知，这个星球是无人居住的？
This planet is uninhabited, to the best of our information?
目前，是的
At present, yes.
- 奇怪  - 有读数？
- Odd. - Getting a reading?
似乎有一些干扰来自那个洞穴
There seems to be some disturbance coming from that cave.
有任何生命形式吗？
Picking up any life-forms?
绝对不是人形生物，舰长
Definitely not humanoid, Captain.
无法确认具体身份
Impossible to make any specific identification.
读数与任何已知信息无关
Readings do not correlate with any known information.
奇怪
That's strange.
那...非常奇怪
That's... very strange.
我在这个地方有一种焦虑的感觉
I'm getting a feeling of anxiety in this place.
听起来很不科学，不是吗？
It doesn't sound very scientific, does it?
但在这里是最强的
But it's strongest right here.
我不知道
I'm not aware of it.
也许这就是你三录仪上显示的东西。
Maybe that's what's registering on your tricorder.
我不知道焦虑能在传感器上显示
I was not aware that anxiety could be registered on sensors.
不能...
No...
当然不能，那...是我
Of course. That's... that's me.
那是我
That's me.
但是，是什么导致的的三录仪做出反应呢？
But what's causing your tricorder to react?
- 你没事吧，舰长？  - 是的，我很好，我...很好
- Are you all right, Captain? - Yes, I'm fine. I'm... fine.
只是对这里发生的事情产生了一些共鸣
Just some sympathetic vibration with what happened here.
让我们回船上
Let's get back to the ship.
我想检查一下斯塔恩斯教授的三录仪的磁带
I want to check out those tapes from Professor Starnes' tricorder.
我要问问那些孩子
And I am going to question those children.
好的，每张卡代表不同的口味
All right. Each card is a different flavor.
随你挑，电脑会混合组合
Take your pick and the computer will mix a combination.
说出你最喜欢的
Call out your favorite.
- 香草！- 巧克力！
- Vanilla! - Chocolate!
好的！
OK!
你想要一个惊喜吗，史蒂夫？
Well. Would you like a surprise, Stevie?
这是椰子和香草，它们都是白的
It's coconut and vanilla. They're both white.
那里，那里，现在
There, there, now.
既有令人不快的惊喜，也有令人愉快的惊喜
There are unpleasant surprises as well as pleasant ones.
那是你不喜欢的，你想来个你喜欢的吗？
That was your unpleasant one. What would you like for your pleasant one?
巧克力旋和开心果
Chocolate wobble and pistachio.
好吧，马上就来了
Well, coming right up.
还有桃子
And peach.
好吧，这将是一个美妙的惊喜
All right. It's going to be a wonderful surprise.
测试显示没有撒谎的迹象
Tests show no evidence of lying.
他们表现得好像没什么问题
They behave as though nothing's wrong.
他们的身体很健康
They're sound physically,
并且没有药物迹象来解释它们目前的状态
and no signs of substances to account for their present state.
- 我没有答案  - 一定有
- I have no answers. - There has to be one.
难道不能等到我们去医院吗？
Can't it wait till we get to a hospital?
我们不会离开，除非我们知道发生了什么，或者正在发生什么
We're not leaving until we know what went on, or what's going on.
我不会阻止你质问他们，但这可能会伤害孩子们
I won't prevent you questioning them, but it could harm the children.
如果我不这样做，对他们来说可能会更糟，对我们也是如此
It could be worse for them if I don't, and for us too.
小心
Be careful.
结束之后，我们可以一起玩游戏。
After this, we can all play games.
从电脑里拿出冰淇淋是什么感觉？
What's it like getting your ice cream out of a computer?
- 这很有趣  - 嗯，你们都玩得很开心
- That was fun. - Well, you're all having a good time.
- 我想我要加入你们，可以吗？  - 请便
- I think I'll join you. Is that OK? - Please do.
好吧，我也要一份冰淇淋
All right. I'll have a dish too.
一份非常小的，它比提拉库斯更好，不是吗？
A very small one. It's better than Triacus, isn't it?
- 那个肮脏的老星球？  - 那地方有什么好的？
- That dirty old planet? - What's so good about that place?
你在那里的时间不长，你不知道
You weren't there very long. You don't know.
- 我认为你们的父母不喜欢它  - 不，他们喜欢
- I don't think your parents liked it. - Yes, they did.
- 我的父母也喜欢  - 父母喜欢愚蠢的事情
- Mine sure did. - Parents like stupid things.
我不确定，父母喜欢孩子
I don't know. Parents like children.
哈，那是你的想法
Ha. That's what you think.
我确定你们的父母爱你们，所以他们带你们去提拉库斯
I'm sure your parents loved you. That's why they took you to Triacus.
这样他们就不会和你们分别很久
So they wouldn't be far away from you for a long time.
那会让他们不高兴，他们会想念你们的
That would make them unhappy. They'd miss you.
我相信你们也会想念他们的
I'm sure that you would miss them too.
忙，忙...
Busy, busy...
忙，忙，忙，忙！
Busy, busy, busy, busy!
孩子：忙，忙，忙，忙！
CHILDREN: Busy, busy, busy, busy!
- 猜猜我们是什么？  - 我知道，一群蜜蜂
- Guess what we are? - I know. A swarm of bees.
小心，小心，我会刺你
Watch out. Watch out. I'll sting you.
现在，等一下
Now, wait a minute.
我们能吃更多的冰淇淋吗？
Can we have more ice cream, please?
不能，它会毁了你的晚餐
I don't think so. It'll spoil your dinner.
看见没？他们都这么说
See? They all say it.
是的
Yeah.
你们度过了忙碌的一天，查佩尔护士会送你们回宿舍
You've had a busy day. Nurse Chapel will see you to your quarters.
非常好的主意，来吧
Very good idea. Come on.
- 我们必须这样做吗？  - 汤米，等一会儿
- Do we have to? - Tommy, just a moment.
我想问你一个问题，来坐下
I'd like to ask you a question. Come and sit down.
你能告诉我你看到了什么吗？
Will you tell me what you saw?
在哪里看到？
Saw where?
在山洞里，在星球上，在提拉库斯
In the cave. On the planet. On Triacus.
- 你在那里  - 你今天看到你父亲了吗？
- You were there. - Did you see your father today?
- 我看到了他  - 他看起来很生气吗？
- I saw him. - Did he seem upset?
- 他很生气  - 为什么生气？
- He was very upset. - What about?
- 我没有问他  - 发生了什么事惹他生气了？
- I didn't ask him. - What was going on to upset him?
我怎么知道？他总是很生气，就像你一样
How should I know? He was always upset, just like you.
我没有生你或你的朋友的气
I'm not upset with you, or your friends.
我们邀请你登上了企业号，如果我不喜欢你，我为什么要这样做？
We invited you aboard the Enterprise. Why would I do that if I didn't like you?
你有你的理由
You have your reasons.
你没有对离开提拉库斯感到不高兴吗？
Aren't you unhappy about leaving Triacus?
那个地方？那里是给成年人的
That place? That's for adults.
你不为离开你的父母而难过吗？
Aren't you upset about leaving your parents?
我的父母？他们喜欢那里
My parents? They love it down there.
总是很忙
Always busy.
他们很高兴
They're happy.
我现在可以走了吗？我也累了，你知道的
Can I go now? I'm tired too, you know.
- 是的，当然，我带你去  - 我认识路
- Yes, certainly. I'll take you. - I know the way.
柯克呼叫安保部门，派人看着孩子们
Kirk to security. Post a guard on the children.
他们要一直处于监视之下
They're to be kept under constant watch.
所有人：冰雹，冰雹，火和雪
ALL: Hail, hail, fire and snow,
呼叫天使，我们要走了
call the angel, we will go,
远远地，看到了
far away, for to see,
友好的天使来找我
friendly angel come to me.
冰雹，冰雹，火和雪
Hail, hail, fire and snow,
呼叫天使，我们要走了
call the angel, we will go,
远远地，看到了
far away, for to see,
友好的天使来找我
friendly angel come to me....
朋友们，你们做得很好
You have done very well, my friends.
你们已经做了必须做的事情
You have done what must be done.
你们已经登上了企业号
You have come aboard the Enterprise.
现在，我们的目的地是联邦殖民地
Now, our destination is a Federation settlement.
柯克舰长无疑会选择离得更近的太空站
Captain Kirk will undoubtedly choose a closer station.
不要让这阻止你们，马科斯十二号星球有数百万人在上面
Do not let that deter you. Marcos XII has millions of people on it.
近百万人将加入我们，成为我们的朋友
Nearly a million will join us as our friends.
其余的将是我们的敌人
The rest will be our enemies.
与其他愿意加入我们的朋友一起，我们将击败我们的敌人
Together with our other friends who will join us, we will defeat our enemies
因为我们在提拉库斯上击败了他们
as we defeated them on Triacus.
马科斯上的一百万朋友将使我们立于不败之地
A million friends on Marcos will make us invincible.
将没人命令我们去哪里，什么时候睡觉，在哪里吃饭
No one will tell us where to go, when to sleep, where to eat.
宇宙将由我来控制，由你们来玩耍
The universe will be mine to command, yours to play in.
为了完成这个伟大的使命，我们必须首先控制企业号
To accomplish this great mission, we must first control the Enterprise.
要控制这艘船，我们首先必须控制船员
To control the ship, we first must control the crew.
你知道怎么做，这是你们的下一个任务
You know how to do that. That is your next task.
你们信什么，你们就做什么，你们就做什么
And as you believe, so shall you do, so shall you do.
As you believe, so shall you do, so shall you do.
你们信什么，你们就做什么，你们就做什么
维持标准轨道
Maintaining standard orbit.
有行星安全小队的报告吗？
Any report from planet's security team?
一切都很安静，长官
Everything is quiet, sir.
我提取了斯塔恩斯教授的磁带中主要的部分
I have extracted the salient portion of Professor Starnes' tapes.
在收集到的技术事实中
Among the technical facts gathered,
他还提出了不科学的假设
he also offered unscientific hypotheses.
让我们看看
Let's see them.
斯塔恩斯：日志日期 5025.3
STARNES: Log date 5025.3.
自从我们抵达提拉库斯以来
Ever since our arrival on Triacus,
我感到日益不安
I've felt a growing feeling of uneasiness.
首先，我将其归因于与新项目相关的常见的神经问题
First, I attributed it to the usual case of nerves associated with a new project.
然而，我发现我的其他同事也受到焦虑的困扰
However, I found the rest of my associates also bothered by anxieties.
唯一没有受到影响的是孩子们
The only ones not affected are the children.
他们发现整件事是一次令人兴奋的冒险
They find the whole thing an exciting adventure.
啊，再次年轻
Ah, to be young again.
让我们再看看这些不科学的假设，史波克先生
Let's see some more of these unscientific hypotheses, Mr. Spock.
5032.4.
我们都有的这种焦虑感越来越严重
The feeling of anxiety we've all been experiencing is growing worse.
还有另一部分，我想你会认为特别有趣
There is another portion which I think you'll find particularly interesting.
5038.3.
威尔金斯教授今天完成了他的挖掘工作
Professor Wilkins finished his excavation today.
虽然这里的文明被一场自然灾害摧毁了
Although the civilization here was destroyed by a natural catastrophe,
看来我们的一个种族在山洞里避难了
it would appear one of our race took refuge in the cave.
对于我们的努力，我们只是变得更加担心
For our efforts, we are becoming only more apprehensive.
仿佛某种看不见的力量正在影响着我们......
As if some unseen force were influencing us...
- 发生了什么事？  - 未知
- What happened? - Unknown.
我没有看到你进来
I didn't see you come in.
我们离开这里后，你能带我们去马科斯十二号星球吗？
After we leave here, can you take us to Marcos XII?
我们可能会带你们去一个联邦星际基地
We'll probably take you to a Federation starbase.
- 我在马科斯十二号上有亲戚  - 对不起
- I have relatives on Marcos XII. - I'm sorry.
它不在我们的巡逻区域内，史波克先生，我们将在我的宿舍里讨论这个问题
It's not in our patrol area. Mr. Spock, we'll pursue this in my quarters.
我可以留在这里观看吗？我会非常安静
Can I stay here and watch? I'll be very quiet.
好的，汤米，上尉，让麦考伊医生到我的宿舍报告
All right, Tommy. Lieutenant, have Dr. McCoy report to my quarters.
莱斯利先生？
Mr. Leslie?
- 嗨，你好  - 嗨
- Hi, there. - Hi.
那是什么？
What is that?
行星提拉库斯
The planet Triacus.
- 我们在这里的时候会一直看到它吗？  - 是的，我们会的
- Will we see it all the time we're here? - Yes, we will.
- 我们在这里的时间里都能看到  - 他在屏幕上看到了提拉库斯
- All the time we're here. - He sees Triacus on the screen.
他以为他看到了
He thinks he sees it.
苏鲁先生，屏幕，我们脱离轨道了
Mr. Sulu, the screen. We're out of orbit.
- 我们很快就会到达马科斯十二号吗？  - 很快
- Will we reach Marcos XII soon? - Very soon.
我们什么时候改变航线的？
When did we change course?
- 我们没有改变航线  - 你是什么意思？
- We haven't changed course. - What do you mean?
- 看看你的控制显示器  - 我们仍然在轨道上
- Look at your control monitor. - We're still in orbit.
你瞎了吗？那不是轨道位置
Have you gone blind? That's not orbiting position.
- 别碰控制器  - 你到底在干什么？
- Don't touch the controls. - What the devil are you doing?
- 我们必须留在这个轨道上  - 你这个瞎子
- We must remain in this orbit. - You blind fool.
你看不见你面前的东西吗？我们不在轨道上
Can't you see what's in front of you? We're not in orbit.
我不会违抗舰桥的命令
I won't disobey orders from the bridge.
你正在违抗命令，现在退到一边
You are. Now step aside.
你正在失去对自己的控制，长官
You're losing control of yourself, sir.
还没有
Not yet.
斯塔恩斯：我受到影响，去做一些没有意义的事情
STARNES: I'm being influenced to do things that do not make sense.
我甚至联系星际舰队司令部
I even went so far as to call Starfleet Command
请求将宇宙飞船用作运输工具
to request a spaceship to be used as a transport.
直到我不知道该运输什么时
It was only when I didn't know what to transport
我才意识到我的思想正在被引导
that I realized my mind was being directed.
我决定向星际舰队发出警告
I decided to send a dispatch to Starfleet, warning them.
上帝宽恕我们，我们必须毁灭自己
God forgive us. We must destroy ourselves.
外星人降临，敌人来自内部
Alien upon us. The enemy from within.
敌人？！
The enemy?!
他没有完成记录，也没有发送急件
He never completed the entry. The dispatch wasn't sent.
除了家庭生活的场景，与孩子们的游戏
Except for scenes of family life, games with the children,
那被完整地记录了
that is the complete record.
无论什么压倒了他们，他们一定做得如此之快
Whatever overwhelmed them must have done so fast.
否则，教授会提供经历的细节
Otherwise the professor would have provided details of the experience.
他是一位出色的科学家，孜孜不倦地追求真理
He was an excellent scientist and tireless in his pursuit of the truth.
- 这可能就是摧毁他的原因  - 邪恶确实试图维持权力
- That could be what destroyed him. - Evil does seek to maintain power
- 通过压制真相  - 或误导无辜者
- by suppressing the truth. - Or misleading the innocent.
误导无辜者？我想知道
Misleading the innocent? I wonder.
你的意思是孩子们可能参与其中吗？
Do you mean the children may be involved?
是的，医生，我们对住在这里的种族了解多少？
Yes, Doctor. What do we know about the race that lived here?
根据传说，提拉库斯是一群掠夺者的所在地
According to legend, Triacus was the seat of a band of marauders
他们在整个爱普西隆印地星系中不断进行战争
who were at constant war throughout Epsilon Indi.
几个世纪后，驱逐舰被他们掠夺的人摧毁
After centuries, the destroyers were destroyed by those they preyed upon.
- 这就是结局吗？  - 不，像许多传说一样
- Is that the end of it? - No. Like so many legends,
这个传说有个可怕的结局
this one has a frightening ending.
它警告说，邪恶正在等待催化剂再次启动它
It warns that the evil is awaiting a catalyst to set it again into motion
并让它穿越银河系
and send it marauding across the galaxy.
邪恶有可能找到催化剂吗？
Is it possible that the evil found the catalyst?
- 我说的是一个传说  - 大多数传说都有其事实依据
- I was speaking of a legend. - Most legends have their basis in fact.
我明白你的意思，但作为医务人员，我必须警告你
I read you, but as medical officer, I must warn you.
除非孩子们释放和宣泄正常的悲伤
Unless the normal grief is tapped and released from these children,
否则你是在踩红线
you are treading dangerously.
我理解你的诊断，我会尊重它
I understand your diagnosis and I'll respect it.
但不会把ii企业号的安全置之度外，谢谢
But not to the exclusion of the safety of the Enterprise. Thank you.
还有哪些探险队访问过提拉库斯？
What other expeditions have visited Triacus?
根据联邦的记录，这是第一次
According to Federation records, this is the first.
斯塔恩斯对看不见的力量有什么看法？
What did Starnes say about the unseen force?
他说，一股看不见的力量正在影响着他
He said an unseen force was influencing him.
他意识到了这一点，与它作斗争，并取消了他要一艘船的请求
He recognized it, was fighting it, and canceled his request for a ship.
一艘船？是的，一艘通往提拉库斯的船，但是为什么？由谁？
A ship? Yes. A ship for Triacus. But why? And by whom?
警卫部队，准备执行救援任务，在传送室集合
Security detachment. Ready for relief duty. Assemble in transporter room.
他们传送上来的时候，我有一些问题要问他们
I'll have questions for that detachment when they're beamed up.
现在是时候让我们弄清楚斯塔恩斯的敌人
It's about time we found out whether Starnes' enemy within
是在下面的星球上还是和我们一起在船上了
is on the planet below or here on board with us.
来吧
Come on.
你们的任务将持续一个小时，准备好你们的通讯器
Your tour of duty will last one hour. Be prepared with your communicators
报告任何外星生物，不要等待调查
to report any alien beings. Don't wait to investigate.
【把警卫部队从提拉库斯传送上来
Beam up the security detachment from Triacus.
史波克？
Spock?
怎么了？
What's wrong?
- 我无法锁定坐标  - 为什么不呢？
- I can't lock on to the coordinates. - Why not?
看来我们不再绕着提拉库斯运行
It appears we are no longer orbiting Triacus.
那不可能
That's impossible.
如果我们不绕着提拉库斯运行，那么我传送下去的人就死了
If we're not orbiting Triacus, the men I beamed down are dead.
舰长，我们不再绕着提拉库斯运行
Captain, we are no longer orbiting Triacus.
激活舰桥监视器屏幕
Activate the bridge monitor screen.
舰长呼叫舰桥，我们没有绕提拉库斯运行
Captain to bridge. We're not orbiting Triacus.
从各方面来看，你都错了，我的屏幕上有提拉库斯
With all respects, you're wrong. I have Triacus on my screen now.
你偏离了轨道，我上来了
You're off course. I'm coming up.
所有人：冰雹，冰雹，火和雪
ALL: Hail, hail, fire and snow,
呼叫天使，我们要走了
call the angel, we will go,
远远地，看到了
far away, for to see,
友好的天使来找我
friendly angel come to me.
苏鲁...
Sulu...
呼叫天使，我们要走了
call the angel, we will go,
远远地，看到了
far away, for to see,
友好的天使来找我
friendly angel come to me.
朋友们，我们已经到了危机时刻
Friends, we have reached a moment of crisis.
敌人发现了我们的行动
The enemy have discovered our operation.
但他们太晚了，他们不再控制这艘船了，是我们在控制
But they are too late. They no longer control the ship. We do.
我们将取得胜利，他们会带我们去任何我们想要的地方
We shall prevail. They will take us any place we desire.
回到你们的岗位，保持你们的控制
So back to your stations. Maintain your controls.
如果抵抗力增加，召唤他们的野兽，他们的野兽会很好地为我们服务
If resistance mounts, call upon their beast. Their beast will serve us well.
他们每个人心中的恐惧都是会吞噬他的野兽
The fear in each one of them is the beast which will consume him.
还记得在提拉库斯上的情况吗？
Remember how it was on Triacus?
如果他们抵抗，在企业号上也应该如此
If they resist, so shall it be on the Enterprise.
如果你们需要我，呼叫我，我会出现
If you need me, call and I will appear.
我们的新目标是马科斯十二号星球
Our new goal is Marcos XII.
这是我们新的开始，我们决不能动摇
It is our new beginning. We must not falter.
去你们的岗位，玛丽，你和我在一起
Go to your stations. Mary, you remain with me.
舵手，忽略你在屏幕上看到的东西，你认为你看到的东西
Helmsman, disregard what you see on the screen, what you think you see.
设定去星际基地4的航线
Set a course for Starbase 4.
- 你听到我说话了吗？  - 是的，长官
- Do you hear me? - Yes, sir.
乌乎拉上尉
Lieutenant Uhura.
联系星际基地4，告诉他们我们把孩子带到那里
Contact Starbase 4. Tell them we're bringing the children there.
告诉星际舰队司令部我怀疑他们实际上是外星人
Tell Starfleet Command I suspect them of being alien in nature
我希望在我们抵达时进行彻底的调查
and I want a thorough investigation made upon our arrival.
是的，长官
Aye, aye, sir.
上尉？
Lieutenant?
- 你在看什么？  - 我看了到我的死亡
- What are you staring at? - I see my death.
漫长的死亡，疾病和疼痛
A long death. Disease and pain.
我看到了我的死亡
I see my death.
- 那里什么都没有  - 哦，上帝！
- There's nothing there. - Oh, God!
舰长，不要让它成为现实
Captain, don't let it be.
史波克先生，你联系星际舰队
Mr. Spock, you make the call to Starfleet.
我命令你改变航线
I ordered you to change course.
苏鲁先生...
Mr. Sulu...
离控制器远点，如果你碰到它们，我们会被摧毁
Stay away from the controls. If you touch them, we'll be destroyed.
苏鲁先生，那里什么都没有
Mr. Sulu, there's nothing there.
舰长，我们为什么要打扰星际舰队？
Captain, why are we bothering Starfleet?
- 这是命令  - 舰桥完全在控制中
- That was an order. - This bridge is under complete control.
- 完全... - 没有必要
- Complete... - There is no need.
看看你周围
Take a look around you.
我不能服从你的命令，舰长
I cannot obey your order, Captain.
把苏鲁先生带到他的宿舍，他被解除职务了
Take Mr. Sulu to his quarters. He's relieved of duty.
[倒着说]
[TALKS BACKWARDS]
你听到我说话了吗？
Did you hear me?
舰长，我们必须从舰桥上下来
Captain, we must get off this bridge.
我们必须...我正在失去指挥权
We must... I'm losing command.
我正在失去指挥的能力
I'm losing my ability to command.
我正在失去企业号
I'm losing the Enterprise.
我正在失去指挥权
I'm losing command.
我正在失去企业号
I'm losing the Enterprise.
这艘船在不断航行
The ship is sailing on and on.
我独自一人
I'm alone.
独自
Alone.
- 我正在失去指挥权  - 舰长
- I'm losing command. - Captain.
我失去了指挥权
I've lost command.
我失去了企业号
I've lost the Enterprise.
吉姆...
Jim...
我获得了指挥权
I've got command.
- 我获得了指挥权  - 是的，舰长
- I've got command. - Correct, Captain.
- 舰长，去哪里？  - 辅助控制，我的瓦肯朋友
- Where to, Captain? - Auxiliary control, my Vulcan friend.
这艘船偏离了航向
This ship is off course.
斯科提
Scotty.
手动控制导航系统，绘制去星际基地4的航线
Override the navigation system and plot a course for Starbase 4.
我做不到，先生
I can't do that, sir.
- 为什么不行？  - 这些是灵敏的仪器
- Why not? - These are sensitive instruments.
我不会让你破坏他们微妙的平衡，我们会迷路，永远迷路
I will not have you upset their delicate balance. We'd be lost, forever lost.
现在走开，走开，否则我们会杀了你
Go away now. Go away or we'll kill you.
斯科提...
Scotty...
听我说，企业号已被外星生物入侵
Listen to me. The Enterprise has been invaded by alien beings.
如果我们把它带到马科斯，数百万人将死亡，像在提拉库斯一样
If we take it to Marcos, millions will die the way they died at Triacus.
不，我没事，史波克，我的野兽被消灭了，它不会回来了
No, I'm all right, Spock. My beast is finished. It won't return.
只要孩子们在场，就会有危险，他们是载体
So long as the children are present, there is danger. They are the carriers.
他们不是外星生物，他们是被误导的孩子
They're not the alien beings. They're children being misled.
他们是追随者，没有他们，邪恶就无法蔓延
They are followers. Without them, evil cannot spread.
他们是孩子
They're children.
企业号上的430名男女
430 men and women on the Enterprise
和飞船本身都受到这些儿童的威胁
and the ship itself are endangered by these children.
他们不知道自己在做什么坏事
They don't know the evil they're doing.
也许这是真的
Perhaps that is true.
但是他们内心的邪恶正在迅速蔓延
But the evil within them is spreading fast
除非我们能找到一种方法来去除它...
and unless we can find a way to remove it...
我们将不得不杀死他们
We'll have to kill them.
- 柯克舰长？  - 这是什么？
- Captain Kirk? - What is it?
我奉命逮捕你和史波克
I have been instructed to place you and Spock under arrest.
- 根据谁的命令？  - 星际舰队司令部，长官
- By whose order? - Starfleet Command, sir.
你从哪里听到的这个命令，少尉？
Where did you hear this order, Ensign?
听我说，这个命令是假的，我希望你们回到你们的岗位
Listen to me. This order is false. I want you to return to your stations.
很抱歉，但我必须坚持你和史波克和我一起去拘留区
Sorry, but I must insist you and Spock come with me to the detention section.
少尉，听我说
Ensign, listen to me.
不要强迫我杀了你，长官，如果有必要，我会的
Do not force me to kill you, sir. I will if I have to.
- 你能安静地过来吗？  - 这个命令是假的，少尉
- Will you come peacefully? - This is a false order, Ensign.
- 我从来没有违抗过命令  - 我知道
- I have never disobeyed an order. - I know that.
- 但是船上有一个外星人  - 我不能违抗
- But there's an alien aboard the ship. - I cannot disobey.
- 你要违抗这个命令！- 星际舰队取代你的命令
- You will disobey this order! - Starfleet supersedes your order.
够了
Enough.
带这些人去拘禁，在舰桥上和我汇合
Take these men to detention and join me on the bridge.
企业号永远不会到达马科斯十二号，它不会降落在那里
Enterprise will never reach Marcos XII. It will not land there.
- 船员们会带我们去，他们相信  - 船员...不明白
- The crew will take us. They believe. - The crew... does not understand.
当他们明白了，他们就不会带你去那里
When they understand, they won't take you there.
- 他们会的！- 我们要去马科斯！
- They will! - We are going to Marcos!
我们要去跟随我们的朋友
We're going to follow our friend.
你们的朋友？那个偷渡者在哪里？他为什么躲起来？
Your friend? Where is that stowaway? Why does he hide?
如果我们呼叫他，他会来的
He will come if we call him.
我们不需要他，我们不怕你
We don't need him. We're not afraid of you.
好，我很高兴你们不怕我
Good. I'm glad you're not afraid of me.
但你们的领导者害怕，他怕什么？
But your leader is afraid. What's he afraid of?
- 他不怕任何人  - 或任何东西
- He's not afraid of anybody. - Or anything.
他害怕被人看到
He's afraid to be seen.
当船员们看到和听到他时
And when the crew sees and hears him,
他们会明白他不是他们的朋友，他们不会跟随他
they'll understand he is not their friend, and they won't follow him.
- 他是我们的朋友  - 那就让他现身
- He is our friend. - Then let him show himself.
让他出来，让他证明他是我的朋友
Bring him out. Let him prove that he is my friend
我会...我会跟随他到宇宙的尽头
and I'll... I'll follow him to the end of the universe.
不！
No!
史波克先生，回放孩子们
Mr. Spock. Play back the chant
为召唤戈尔甘而唱的圣歌
the children sang to summon up the Gorgan.
冰雹，冰雹，火和雪
Hail, hail, fire and snow,
呼叫天使，我们要走了
call the angel, we will go,
远远地，看到了
far away, for to see,
友好的天使来找我
friendly angel come to me.
冰雹，冰雹，火和雪
Hail, hail, fire and snow,
呼叫天使，我们要走了
call the angel, we will go,
远远地，看到了
far away, for to see,
友好的天使来找我
friendly angel come to me.
现在是看清世界本来面目的时候了
The time has come to see the world as it is.
来吧
Come on.
谁召见了我？
Who has summoned me?
是我，戈尔根，我的野兽走了
I did, Gorgan. My beast has gone.
它在现实的光芒下失去了力量，我又能指挥了
It lost its power in the light of reality. I command again.
我在这里命令你
And I ordered you here.
不，舰长，我在这里指挥
No, Captain. I command here.
我的追随者是坚强、忠诚和顺从的
My followers are strong and faithful and obedient.
这就是为什么我们无论走到哪里都会带走属于我们的东西
That's why we take what is ours wherever we go.
你从那些不认识你的人那里拿走
You take from those who do not know you.
而我们认识你
And we know you.
- 那你知道我一定会赢  - 如果我们联合起来对抗你就不会
- Then you know I must win. - Not if we join together to fight you.
愚蠢，你会被毁灭的
Foolish. You will be destroyed.
我想请你加入我，但你很温柔
I would ask you to join me, but you are gentle.
这是一个致命的弱点
And that is a grave weakness.
- 我们也非常强大  - 力量被温柔抵消
- We are also very strong. - Strength is canceled by gentleness.
你充满了善良，比如你不能被改变
You are full of goodness. Such as you cannot be changed.
你就像父母们一样，你必须被消灭
You were like the parents. You must be eliminated.
孩子们，我有你们在提拉库斯上的照片，你们想看看吗？
Children, I have pictures of you on Triacus. Would you like to see?
史波克先生？图片呢？
Mr. Spock? The pictures?
我禁止
I forbid it.
- 你为什么要害怕它？  - 我没有害怕
- Why should you fear it? - I fear nothing.
正如我们听说的，史波克先生，照片，孩子们在等着
So we were told. Mr. Spock, the pictures. The children are waiting.
他们不会帮我们运送，他们反对我们
They would not help transport us. They were against us.
他们必须被消灭
They had to be eliminated.
汤米的父亲本来要毁灭你，但他为时已晚
Tommy's father would have destroyed you, but he was too late.
你也来不及了，善良的人总是这样
You were also too late. The kind ones always are.
并非总是如此，这次不是
Not always. Not this time.
你不能隐瞒他们，他们就像我们一样能看到你
You can't hide from them. They see you as we see you.
他们知道你是什么
They know what you are.
- 孩子们也会学习  - 你们是我未来的将军
- Even the children learn. - You are my future generals.
我们可以一起组建追随者大军，去你们的岗位上
Together we can raise armies of followers. Go to your posts.
第一次伟大的胜利就在我们身上，你会看到的
The first great victories are upon us. You will see.
我们在马科斯十二号上有数百万朋友
We have millions of friends on Marcos XIII.
我们将消灭所有反对我们的人
We shall exterminate all who oppose us.
我们的目标不能被那些不同意
Our purpose cannot be contaminated by those who disagree,
不理解的人污染
who do not understand.
- 他们必须被消灭  - 不要害怕
- They must be annihilated. - Don't be afraid.
看看他
Look at him.
没有你们这些孩子，他就什么都不是
Without you children, he's nothing.
邪恶依然存在于他的内心
The evil remains within him.
我命令你们！我命令你们！
I command you! I command you!
去你们的岗位，履行你们的职责，否则我会摧毁你们
To your posts. Carry out your duties or I will destroy you.
你将被扫到一边为强者让路
You will be swept aside to make way for the strong.
看看他到底有多丑，看着他，不要害怕
Look how ugly he really is. Look at him and don't be afraid.
死亡，你们都去死，你们都去死
Death. Death to you all. Death to you all.
你们都去死
Death to you all.
没事了
It's all right.
他们在哭，我不知道是怎么回事，但很乐意看到
They're crying. I don't know how it happened, but it's good to see.
没事了，没事了，不是吗，医生？
It's all right. It's all right, isn't it, Doctor?
是的，没事了
Yes, it's all right.
我们现在可以帮助他们了
We can help them now.
- 马科斯十二号就在前面，长官  - 调转航向，苏鲁先生
- Marcos XII dead ahead, sir. - Reverse course, Mr. Sulu.
航线已调转，舰长
Course reversed, Captain.
- 设定去星际基地4的航线  - 是的，长官
- Set course for Starbase 4. - Yes, sir.